Guide to the Martin Harwit papers, 1957-1987
Harwit, Martin papers, 1957-1987
- II. Program in the History and Philosophy of Science and Technology (HPST)
  - HPST Advisory Committee, 1985-86 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - HPST annual reports, 1985-86, 1986-87 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - HPST courses (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - HPST finances (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - HPST secretary (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - A (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - B (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - C (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Colloquia, 1984-85 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Colloquia, 1985-86 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Colloquia, 1986-87 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Colloquia, 1987-88 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Common Learning (Box 8, Folder 26-27)
  - Cornell guidelines (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - D (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Dean's office (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Development Office (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Development Office - private foundations (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - F (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Field membership list (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Field vitae (Box 8, Folder 35-36)
  - Graduate field (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Graduate field proposal (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Graduate school (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - H (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - G (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - I, J (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - K (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - L (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Library collections (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - M (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Mailing list (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - N (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF) proposal (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - NSF policy - National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - O (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - P, Q (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Pittsburgh meeting, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Provost's office (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - R (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - S (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Student travel/fellowships (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Search Committee (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Search Committee - Communication Arts search (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Search Committee - Technology search (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Search Committee - Job search (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Search Committee - Job search: 20th century physics, 1986-87 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Society for the Humanities (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Society for the Humanities - focal theme (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Society for the Humanities - focal theme (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - T (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - U, V (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Concentration (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - W (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Williams, L. Pearce (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - X, Y, Z (Box 9, Folder 7)
- III. Common Learning Program
  - Common Learning, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 8-10)
  - Common Learning, 1985-86 (Box 9, Folder 11-12)
  - Common Learning handouts in courses (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - A, 1984-87 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Burke Interferometry Workshop, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Thomas M. Donohue correspondence, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - F, 1985-87 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - G, 1985-86 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - H, 1985-87 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - I, 1986-87 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - J, 1984-85 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - K, 1985-86 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - L, 1984-85 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Franklin D. Martin meeting, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - M, 1985-87 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - National Commission of Space (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - N, 1985-87 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - N, 1985-86 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Newton/Pellerin correspondence, 1985-86 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Newton/Pellerin correspondence, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - P, 1985-86 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Harvey Tananbaum meeting, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - T, 1985-87 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Valerie Neal brochure (Box 9, Folder 34-35)
  - Valerie Neal correspondence, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Transparencies (Box 9, Folder 37)
- IV. Astrophysics Management Operations Working Group (AMOWG)
  - AMOWG program group, 1984-85 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - AMOWG Council meetings, minutes, agendas, 1984-85 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - AMOWG Council meetings, minutes, agendas, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - AMOWG Council meeting, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - AMOWG Council meeting, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 43-45)
  - AMOWG Council meeting, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 1-6)
  - AMOWG Council meeting, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 8-10)
  - Harvey Tananbaum group (Box 10, Folder 11)
- V. Space and Earth Science Advisory Committee (SESAC)
  - SESAC - general matters (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - SESAC - appointment as NASA consultant, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - L.J. Lanzerotti correspondence (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - SESAC minutes of old meetings, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - SESAC minutes of old meetings, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - SESAC meeting, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 17-18)
  - SESAC "Collected Letters and Testimony: Task Force on Scientific Uses of Space Station", 1984-85 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - SESAC minutes, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - SESAC minutes, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 21-29)
  - SESAC 1988 budget, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - SESAC minutes, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Explorer Program projections (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - "NASA News", 1987 (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
  - SESAC meeting, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
  - NASA reports, 1986-87 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Agreement between the U.S. and U.S.S.R. re outer space exploration (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Space and Earth Science Committee meeting, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Research Corporation, 1973-76 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- VI. Research Projects
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 1965-67 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Research Corporation report, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF) - GP 8471, 1968-69 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Research Corporation, 1970-73 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - NSF grant; Hydrogen - GP 1338, 1963-64 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - NSF grant; Hydrogen - GP 1338, 1965-66 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - NSF grant; Hydrogen - GP 1338, 1967-68 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - NSF grant; Infrared Extended Sources, 1965-67 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - NSF grant; GP 7008, 1967-68 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Invitation for space flight participation, 1968-69 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - New York State Science and Technology Foundation, 1966-69 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Anderson Time Delay Study (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Gravitational Time Delay, NSG-7268 (Box 11, Folder 22-23)
  - Gravitational Time Delay, proposals and reports, 1973-74 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Gravitational Time Delay, proposals and reports, 1974-76 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Gravitational Time Delay, proposals and reports, 1977-79 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - NSF report and correspondence, 1970-73 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Out of Ecliptic Mission, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Out of Ecliptic Mission, 1977-78 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Solar Polar Mission, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 30-32)
  - Solar Polar Mission, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Solar Polar Mission, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Solar Polar Mission, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
  - Solar Polar Mission, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Solar Polar Mission, articles and reports (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Solar Polar Mission research proposal, 1978-86 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Czechoslovak proposal, 1972-74 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - USSR and Eastern Europe, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Patents, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Proposal for the Lear Jet Aircraft, 1981-82 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Lear Jet project, 1976-77 (Box 12, Folder 11-12)
  - Lear Jet project, 1978-81 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Lear Jet project, 1981-84 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Lear Jet proposal, 1977-78 (Box 12, Folder 15-16)
  - Lear Jet proposal, 1978-79 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Lear Jet proposal, 1974-76 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Submillimeter Astronomical Spectrometry from Aircraft, 1971-72 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Submillimeter Astronomical Spectrometry from Aircraft, 1972-73 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Submillimeter Astronomical Spectrometry from Aircraft proposal, 1973-74 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Submillimeter Astronomical Spectrometry from Aircraft, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 22-23)
  - Submillimeter Astronomical Spectrometry from Aircraft, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Submillimeter Astronomical Spectrometry from Aircraft, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Airborne Infrared and Submillimeter Astronomical Polarization Measurements at Different Wavelengths (C-141 Aircraft), 1972-79 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Airborne Infrared and Submillimeter Astronomical Polarization Measurements at Different Wavelengths, 1976-78 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - NSF regulations (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - NASA-Ames grant no. 33-010-146 (Box 12, Folder 29-30)
  - Research proposal for "Infrared Lines from Shocked Galactic Gases", 1979-83 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Proposal for Development of Gallium Arsenide Detectors for Far-Infrared Space Astronomy at 200-350u, 1982-83 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Proposal for a Study of [OI] 63.2 and 145.5 Micron Emission from M17 and SgrA from the Lear Jet, 1982-83 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Proposal for 157um [C II] Observations of the Galactic Center and Developments of Detectors for 200um, 1981-82 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Proposal for the High-Resolution Infrared spectroscopic Observations from Aircraft, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - NSF Three Year Proposal: The Role of Theory and Analytical Observations in the Development of Astronomy, 1981-84 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Proposal for Development of Gallium Arsenide Detectors for Far-Infrared Space Astronomy at 200-350u, 1982-83 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Proposal for the Growth in Understanding of the Universe, 1984-87 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Proposal for Polarization Studies from 16 to 30um from the Kuiper Airborne Observatory (KAO), 1981-82 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Proposal for Interdisciplinary Scientist on Shuttle Infrared Telescope Facility (SIRTF), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Research Proposal (with German investigators) for Mapping of the CI 609u Line in Molecular Clouds (using the C141) (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Proposal for Interdisciplinary Scientist in SIRTF, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Proposal for Models of Infrared and Submillimeter Sources, 1983-86 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Proposal for the NASA Graduate Student Researchers Program, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Proposal for Construction and Testing of Stressed Gallium-Doped Germanium Photoconductive Detectors for Far-Infrared Astronomy, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Proposal for Radiation Transport Modelling in Infrared Astronomy Applications to the Space Infrared Telescope Facility, 1985-88 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Proposal for 350 and 450 Micron Spectroscopy from a Ground-Based Site, 1981-84 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Proposal for Airborne Infrared and Submillimeter Astronomical Polarization Measurements at Different Wavelengths (C-141 Aircraft), 1977-79 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Proposal for Infrared Spectral Line Observations from the KAO (C-141), 1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Proposal for Far Infrared Spectral Line Observations from the KAO (C-141), 1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Proposal for Far Infrared Spectral Line Observations from the KAO (C-141), 1980-81 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Proposal for Far Infrared Spectral Line Observations from the KAO (C-141), 1981-82 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Proposal for Far Infrared Spectral Line Observations from the KAO (C-141), 1982-83 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Proposal for Far Infrared Spectral Line Observations from the KAO (C-141), 1983-83 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Proposal for Far Infrared Spectral Line Observations from the KAO (C-141), 1984-85 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Proposal for Far Infrared Spectral Line Observations from the KAO (C-141), 1985-86 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Proposal to NASA for an Airborne Hadamard Transform Spectrometer for 20u Astronomical Observations at a Resolution of 0.5 CM-1, 1973-74 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Proposal to NASA for Submillimeter Astronomical Spectrometry from the Lear Jet Aircraft, 1979-81 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Proposal to NASA for Submillimeter Astronomical Spectrometry from the Lear Jet Aircraft, 1980-81 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Proposal to NASA for Submillimeter Astronomical Spectrometry from the Lear Jet Aircraft, 1981-82 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Proposal to NASA for Submillimeter Astronomical Spectrometry from the Lear Jet Aircraft, 1982-83 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Proposal to NASA for Submillimeter Astronomical Spectrometry from the Lear Jet Aircraft, 1983-84 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Proposal for Support of Far-Infrared Galactic Fine-Structure Emission (Lear Jet), 1985-86 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Proposal to NASA for 100u Observations of Comet Kohoutek with the Cornell Liquid Helium cooled Photometer/Spectrometer, 1973-74 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Proposal to NSF for Theoretical Solar System Studies, 1974-75 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Proposal to NASA for Viking: Two Experiments in Gravitational time Delay (Polarization Dependence and Dappler Ranging), 1977-79 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Proposal to NASA for Procedures for Dealing with Certain Types of Noise and Systematic Errors Common to Many Hadamard Transform Optical Systems, 1975-76 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Proposal to NASA for "Is IRAS Cirrus Cloud Emission Largely Fine-Structure Radiation?", 1985-86 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Project Operating Plan for the 91-CM Airborne Infrared Observatory, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Research paper: "Galactic and Extragalactic Infrared Spectrometer from NASA Aircraft" (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Lear Jet and KAO publications list (NASA-Ames Research Center), 1984 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics (AIAA) paper: "Airloads near the Open Port of a One-Meter Airborne Telescope", 1975 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - KAO Users' Group, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 32-34)
  - KAO Users' Group (hand-written notes), 1980-81 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - KAO Users' Group correspondence, bulletins, and memos, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 36-37)
  - Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL) Contract No. 957701, "Infrared Astronomical Satellite (IRAS) General Investigator Program", 1987 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - NASA-SADAP Proposal Type 2, "Models for Far-Infrared Extragalactic sources", 1987 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - KAO Users' Group, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - KAO Users' Group, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
  - KAO Users' Group, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 4-7)
  - KAO Users' Group, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Reports re. KAO Users' Group, 1982-84 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - KAO Development Plan, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - KAO Users' Group, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - KAO Users' Group, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 12-13)
  - Lear Jet report to Users' Group (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Ames Research Center Users' Group notes, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Ames Research Center Users' Group, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Proposal for High Resolution Cryogenic Grating Spectrometer to Study Far Infrared Lines from the KAO, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Annual KAO Users' Meeting, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Dead proposals (Box 14, Folder 19-22)
  - Dead proposal: Planets - Hadamard (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - A Multi-Band Far-Infrared Survey with a Balloon-Borne Telescope (Box 14, Folder 24-28)
  - Hoffman - Balloon (Box 14, Folder 29-30)
  - Proposals and calls (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Department of Transportation - Far-Infrared Atmospheric Emission Spectrometry (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - 8464 - Goddard, NAS 5-26669: Construction and Testing of Stressed Gallium-Doped Germanium Photoconductive Detectors for Far-Infrared Astronomy (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - NSF - Soc 75-15804 8370 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
  - Langley NSG 1263 U25-8371: "Procedures for Dealing with Certain Types of Noise and Systematic Errors common to Many Hadamard Transform Optical Systems" (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - NGR 33-010-210: "High Resolution 10-micron Spectrometry at Different Planetary Latitudes" (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - NGR 33-010-210 (Box 15, Folder 5-7)
  - NGR 33-010-210, Kitt Peak National Observatory, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Final report: Development and Evaluation of a Hadamard Transform Imaging Spectrometer and a Hadamard Transform Thermal Imager (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Air Force Cambridge Research Laboratories (AFCRL) F19628-74-C-0110: "Observations of Jupiter with a Hadamard Transform Spectrometer" (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - AFCRL - Vanasse, 1972-74 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - AFCRL - Vanasse, 1970-71 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - AFCRL - F19628-74-C-0110, 1973-76 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - AFCRL - Proposal and reports for "Spectrometer for Far Infrared Astronomy" (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - European Astroplane Observatory (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Submillimeter Local Oscillators for Spaceborne Heterodyne Applications (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - NASA Technical Memorandum: Telescope Systems for Balloon-Borne Research (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - NASA's Airborne Astronomy Program: Accomplishments and Potential (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Interim Study Report for Cosmic Background Explorer: appendixes, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 19-20)
  - Far Infrared Spectrometry of the Cosmic Background Radiation - John C. Mather Ph.D. thesis, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - The Infrared Telescope on Spacelab 2 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - 100 micron Detector Development Program (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Rocket-Borne Liquid Helium Cooled Telescope (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Superfluid-Helium-Cooled Rocket-Borne Far-Infrared Radiometer (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Final report: Large Deployable Reflector (LDR), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - LDR System Concept and Technology Definition Study Kickoff, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 27-28)
  - LDR Transportation Structures (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - LDR - Science Briefing (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - The Shuttle Infrared Telescope Facility (SIRTF) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - SIRTF - Design Optimization Study final Technical Report, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - SIRFT - Report of the Focal Plane Instruments and Requirements Science Team and the SIRFT Science Working Group, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - SIRFT - Phase A concept Description; SIRFT Newsletter #3, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - SIRFT - Technological Readiness Review, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - SIRFT - NASA Announcement of Opportunity, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - A Proposal for Development of a High Resolution Cryogenic Grating Spectrometer to Study Far-Infrared Lines from KAO (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - A Proposal for Flight of a Contaminant Radiation Monitor and Infrared Background Mapper on the Space Shuttle Orbital Flight Test Missions, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - A Proposal for Flight of a Contaminant Radiation Monitor and Infrared Background Mapper on the Space Shuttle Orbital Flight Test Missions - Management and Cost Plan, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - A Proposal for Flight of a Contaminant Radiation Monitor and Infrared Background Mapper on the Spacelab 2 Mission - Management and Cost Plan, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 10-11)
  - A Proposal for Spacelab I for the Design, Fabrication, Test, and Flight of an Advanced Technology Radiometer, Column Density and Infrared Background Monitor, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - A Large-Aperture Space Telescope for Infrared and Submillimeter Astronomy (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Optical Telescope Assembly Project Report: Space Telescope Performance Study Final Report, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - German Infrared Laboratory - Wissenschaftliche Instrumentierung, Beobachtungsprogramme und Mission, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Astrophysics and the Space Station: Volumes 1 and 2, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Astrophysics and the Space Station: Volumes 3-5, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Astronomical Data Notebook, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Astronomical Data Notebook, 1974-75 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Astronomical Data Notebook, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - "Solar System Spectrophotometry," a research report, 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Research papers on Multiplex Grating Spectrometers (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Infrared Astronomy Notebook, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Notes on Hadamard Transform Spectrometry (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Notes on Hadamard Transform Optics (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - "Coded Aperture Imaging," to be published in Imaging in Diagnostic Medicine (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Various research articles re. Hadamard Transform Spectrometers, 1949-71 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Various research articles on Spectrometers, 1966-69 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Various research articles re. Hadamard Transform Spectrometers, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Hadamard Transform Spectrometers, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Hadamard Transform Spectrometers, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Hadamard Transform Spectrometers, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 3-4)
  - Hadamard Transform Spectrometers, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Hadamard Transform Spectrometers, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Hadamard Transform Spectrometers, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 7-8)
  - Hadamard Transform Spectrometers, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 9-11)
  - Hadamard Transform Spectrometers, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Hadamard Transform Spectrometers, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Proposal requests and studies, 1974-75 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Near Infrared Background Experiment (NIRBE), Shuttle Facility Mission, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Proposal to NASA for a Small Helium-Cooled Infrared Telescope for Spacelab, P780-4-78, 1978-81 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Proposal to Scholarly Studies program at the Smithsonian Institution for Construction of a High Sensitivity Multibeam Photometer for Far-Infrared Astronomy, SS 18-2-79, 1979-80 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Proposal to NASA for "The Reflight of the Spacelab 2 Infrared Telescope", 1981-84 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Proposal to NASA in response to AO-OSS-2-78 for Spacelab Missions, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Proposal to NASA for "Infrared Lines from Shocked Galactic Gases", 1979-83 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Draft report: Infrared Panel Astronomy Survey Committee, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Shuttle study reports, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Proposal to NASA for a Preliminary Design Study of an Orbiting Astronomical Observatory (IR-OAO) (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Draft proposal for Construction of a Radiant Cooler for Space Experiments, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - General Design Constraints for Small Astronomy Satellite (SAS), 1969-72 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Infrared Astronomical Satellite (IRAS) concept description, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Infrared Satellite proposal, 1974-75 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Infrared Astronomy Working Group (IAWG), 1972 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Report of the Joint Scientific Mission Definition Team for and IRAS, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Cryogenic Infrared Astronomy Satellite (CIRAS) Preliminary Feasibility Assessment (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Proposal to NASA for "Mission Definition for a Far-Infrared Astronomical Explorer Satellite", 1974 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Proposal for "An Infrared Survey of the Celestial Sphere," Jet Propulsion Laboratory, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Shuttle Infrared Telescope (SIRTF) Design Study, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Astronomy Mission Board, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
  - Final Report F/193-4-00 Riverside Research Institute (RRI) Reduction of Celestial Mapping Program (CMP) Data (U), Volume I, 1971-72 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Cryogenic Society Workshop, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - NASA-Cryogenic Engineering, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - "Infrared Astronomical and Engineering Test Satellite" (a proposal to NASA), 1974-76 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - "Orbiting Cryogenic Infrared Astronomical Telescope: An Environmental Research Satellite Study," Volume I, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - "Orbiting Cryogenic Infrared Astronomical Telescope: An Environmental Research Satellite Study," Volume II, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Space Astronomy (CSA) (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - "The Effect of the Shuttle Contaminant Environment on a Sensitive Infrared Telescope" (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Astronomy on the Shuttle Sortie, 1972-80 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - An All-Sky Survey for Far-Infrared Radiation Associated with High Energy Phenomena, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Recommendation to the National Academy of Sciences Concerning the Establishment of a National Infrared Astronomical Facility (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - "Effects of Surface Contamination on the Infrared Emissivity and Visible-light Scattering of Highly Reflective Surfaces at Cryogenic Temperatures", 1972 (Box 18, Folder 16)